cdw.com 2017-02-04

# Terms and Conditions - Privacy Policy

### At CDW, we understand that your privacy is an important part of the trust you place in us. This Policy explains how personal information of CDW customers is collected, used and disclosed by CDW LLC and its U.S. subsidiaries and affiliated companies ("CDW" or "We"). This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to the websites, online activities, and online services of CDW, including CDW.com and CDW’s mobile applications (collectively, "our Sites") where we post our Policy. Except for CDW’s own online activities on third-party websites and online services where we post our Policy, this Policy does not apply to, and CDW is not responsible for, any other data practices of third-party websites and online services or the practices of other third parties. To learn about third-party data practices, please visit their respective privacy policies. This Policy also does not apply to CDW websites or online services that display or link to different privacy statements.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect information about you in various ways, including the following. 

**Information You Provide**

We collect information you provide us when you use our Sites. For example, we collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, demographics, and other information you provide us online. We also collect credit card numbers and other forms of payment information if you purchase products and services through our Sites and certain third-party sites.

**Information from Other Sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Sites. As examples, we may obtain demographic data from third-party data providers to better market to you, and we may purchase or lease lists from list brokers to correct or supplement your data.

**Information Automatically Collected**

When you visit our Sites, some information about your visit is automatically collected by CDW’s systems. For example, when you visit our Sites your computer's or mobile device’s operating system, application software, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, peripherals, and the websites you visited before our Sites are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Sites including information about your orders, purchases, and cart activity.

  * **Cookies.** We automatically collect information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites and your experience. As examples, we use cookies to see which areas and features are popular, to count visits to our Sites and to deliver personalized ads. 
  * **Web Beacons.** We also collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images used on our Sites and in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**Online Tracking by Third Parties**

Other third parties may collect information about you through our Sites, including personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Sites. Some third parties provide us with analytics services and automatically collect the type of information described above. Some third parties collect information on behalf of CDW and others for online advertising purposes described below.

**ONLINE ADVERTISEMENTS**

We may use information collected using our own and third-party cookies and Web beacons on our Sites and in our emails to deliver CDW advertising displayed to you on third-party sites and social networking services. We use cookie information to know when you return to our Sites after visiting these third-party sites and services. We use this information and other information about you, including order and cart activity information, to try to understand your interests and show you relevant advertising and information about products and services offered by CDW and its partners. To learn about your choices regarding CDW’s use of its own cookies to deliver personalized ads, click here.

Certain third-party ad services may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, and the browser you use to visit our Sites. They do this using their own cookies, Web beacons or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising relevant to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Sites and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third-party cookies or Web beacons, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about the practices of many common ad services, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed). If you would like more information about the practices of social networking services you use where CDW ads are displayed, please visit the respective privacy policies of those services.

**USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We use personal information collected online for purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services. For example, we may use information that you provide or about you to: 

  * provide and deliver products and services you request;
  * send you transaction related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, product and services information, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * operate and improve our Sites, products and services;
  * facilitate the provision of software updates, product support, and other services related to our mobile applications;
  * process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * ask you to take part in research and surveys used to measure our performance and improve our products, services and customer experience;
  * send you catalogs and communicate with you about new contests, promotions and rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by CDW and our selected partners;
  * link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs, customize our offerings to those needs and provide you with better service.

CDW may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. 

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Ways we may share your personal information with third parties include the following: 

  * with your consent;
  * with trusted third parties for their own marketing purposes in compliance with applicable laws and subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * with third-party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and need access to your information to do that work;
  * with suppliers and distributors to CDW for their internal purposes including administrative purposes; to improve performance, products and services; and for purposes relating to proposed or completed transactions facilitated by CDW; 
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of CDW, our agents, customers, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of CDW, its customers, or any person;
  * in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information in a form that does not directly identify you. 

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

CDW takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES**

**Email Choices**

You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails from CDW by following the instructions in those emails. To manage your email subscription, click here. To manage your Catalog subscription, click here. You may also make requests about your contact preferences and changes to your information by contacting your account manager. If you do not know your account manager, simply click here. If you opt-out of promotional emails, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations.

**Access and Change Requests**

You may correct some personal and account information maintained in your E-Account through your E-Account. To request access to, or the correction or removal of any other information about you or content you post on our Sites, please contact your account manager. If you do not know your account manager, simply click here or call 866.782.4239. We reserve the right to decline requests unless required by applicable law.

**Online Tracking Choices**

When you visit our Site, we and others give you the following choices about use of mechanisms for tracking, including tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites and online services by third parties. Many Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies from CDW and others. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site. You can choose to opt-out of use of cookies by certain third-party advertising networks to deliver ads tailored to your profile and preferences. To find out more and opt-out [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed) or visit our About Cookies page. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice. Please visit the respective privacy policies and/or review the privacy settings of the social networking services you use for the choices about CDW ads on those services. While we and others give you choices described in this Policy, there are many ways Web browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and we may not be aware of or honor every mechanism.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

CDW may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date below.

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us by [clicking here](mailto:CDWWay@cdw.com). 

Version Date: 10/16/2014
